[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[Pretty Guardian of the City]
[الحارس الجميل للمدينة]
[Episode 23]
[الحلقة 23]
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Stop drinking.
توقف عن الشرب.
You've drunk too much.
لقد شربت كثيرا.
Waiter.
نادل.
More wine.
مزيد من الخمر.
Stop drinking.
توقف عن الشرب.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
How have you been?
كيف كان حالك؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Take it away.
خذه بعيدا.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Stop drinking.
توقف عن الشرب.
Let go!
اتركه!
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
Let me drown my sorrows.
دعني أغرق أحزاني.
What brought you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Are you worried about me?
هل أنت قلق بشأني؟
You regret it, right?
أنت نادم على ذلك ، أليس كذلك؟
Y-Young Master.
Y- يونغ ماستر.
It's you.
انه انت.
You look so upset.
تبدو مستاء جدا.
How about
ماذا عن
I play a song
ألعب أغنية
to cheer you up?
ليهتف لك؟
Yunxi.
يونشى.
Girl.
بنت.
Fusheng,
فوشينغ ،
if anything bad happens in the future,
إذا حدث أي شيء سيء في المستقبل ،
I'll have to leave my brother to you.
سأضطر إلى ترك أخي لك.
Besides your brother,
إلى جانب أخيك ،
I'm afraid there's someone else
أخشى أن يكون هناك شخص آخر
you're also worried about.
أنت قلق أيضًا.
Love is painful sometimes.
الحب مؤلم احيانا
You can't be with the one you love
لا يمكنك أن تكون مع من تحب
and are not able to get over him.
ولا يستطيعون تجاوزه.
The more you love him,
كلما كنت تحبه ،
the more deeply you get hurt.
كلما تأذيت بعمق.
Girl,
بنت،
you should've learned your lesson.
يجب أن تكون قد تعلمت الدرس الخاص بك.
Let it go.
دعها تذهب.
Yunxi!
يونشى!
Young Master got wasted because of you.
السيد الشاب ضاع بسببك.
He's devastated.
إنه محطم.
But you!
لكنك!
You're actually
أنت في الحقيقة
enjoying yourself
الاستمتاع بنفسك
in another man's arms.
بين ذراعي رجل آخر.
How could you do this to me?
كيف يمكنك أن تفعل هذا بي؟
No.
رقم.
To our Young Master?
لسيدنا الشاب؟
What I and Yunxi do
ما أفعله أنا و Yunxi
has nothing to do with you.
لا علاقة لك به.
If I weren't in a hurry,
إذا لم أكن في عجلة من أمري ،
I would beat you up.
كنت سأضربك.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
To see Young Master.
لرؤية السيد الشاب.
Since I've decided to leave,
منذ أن قررت المغادرة ،
I don't want to get involved with him anymore.
لا أريد التورط معه بعد الآن.
Young Master
المعلم الصغير
loves you with his whole heart.
يحبك من كل قلبه.
He's now heartbroken because of you
إنه الآن محزن القلب بسببك
and wouldn't stop drinking in the hotel.
ولن أتوقف عن الشرب في الفندق.
Aren't you supposed to check on him?
ألا يفترض بك أن تتفحصه؟
No.
رقم.
Yunxi, I was wrong about you.
يونشى ، كنت مخطئا بشأنك.
I never knew you were so cruel.
لم أكن أعلم أنك كنت بهذه القسوة.
Young Master shouldn't have loved you.
لا ينبغي أن يحبك السيد الشاب.
He was just wasting his time!
كان فقط يضيع وقته!
Girl,
بنت،
if you can't get over him,
إذا لم تستطع التغلب عليه ،
don't push yourself too hard.
لا تدفع نفسك بقوة.
Go and see him.
اذهب وشاهده.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
Let's drink.
لنشرب.
Yunxi.
يونشى.
Don't leave me.
لا تتركنى.
Please don't leave me.
من فضلك لا تتركني.
Young Master and Yunxi
السيد الشاب و Yunxi
are a couple of fickle lovers.
زوجان من العشاق المتقلبين.
One was in another man's arms
كان أحدهما في ذراعي رجل آخر
shedding tears of joy.
تذرف دموع الفرح.
The other is holding another girl's hand
الآخر يمسك بيد فتاة أخرى
and being so lovey-dovey.
وكونه محبوبًا جدًا.
So I'm the only one who hasn't moved on.
لذا فأنا الوحيد الذي لم ينتقل.
♫The longing is mysterious like a misty rain♫
♫ الشوق غامض مثل المطر الضبابي
♫Her tenderness stirs up deep and ceaseless affection♫
حنانها يثير عاطفة عميقة ومتواصلة
Yunxi,
يونشى ،
I just want to tell you
انا فقط اريد ان اخبرك
♫The oath is about to be spoken but stopped♫
القسم على وشك النطق ولكن توقف ♫
that I've fallen in love with you.
أنني وقعت في حبك.
♫Afraid that the dream will shatter♫
تخشى أن ينكسر الحلم
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
We will
ونحن سوف
♫It’s hard to rewrite the ending even after half a lifetime of repentance♫
♫ من الصعب إعادة كتابة النهاية حتى بعد نصف عمر من التوبة ♫
be happy together.
كن سعيدا معا.
I saved you three times.
لقد أنقذتك ثلاث مرات.
We're destined to be together.
نحن مقدرون أن نكون معا.
♫We meet in the fragrance of sweet-scented osmanthus as the rain knocks♫
♫ نلتقي برائحة الأوسمانثوس الحلوة مع دقات المطر ♫
You can't escape me.
لا يمكنك الهروب مني.
♫Smiling under the umbrella brings back the longing again♫
الابتسام تحت المظلة يعيد الشوق من جديد
♫The one with desire can't help that the other does not reciprocate♫
من لديه رغبة لا يستطيع أن يساعده أن الآخر لا يبادله
♫Heartbreaking zither music fills my dream for the rest of my life♫
موسيقى آلة القانون المفجعة تملأ حلمي لبقية حياتي
Keep it in mind.
ضع ذلك في الاعتبار.
You only belong to me.
أنت فقط ملك لي.
♫There is no cure for the romantic longing that causes inconsolable heartache♫
♫ لا يوجد علاج للشوق الرومانسي الذي يسبب وجع قلب لا يطاق
Now that I've tied the red string around your wrist,
الآن بعد أن ربطت الخيط الأحمر حول معصمك ،
you're mine.
أنت لي.
♫Clearly interested but biased against the one with desire♫
مهتم بوضوح لكنه متحيز ضد صاحب الرغبة
♫We meet in the fragrance of sweet-scented osmanthus as the rain knocks♫
♫ نلتقي برائحة الأوسمانثوس الحلوة مع دقات المطر ♫
Yunxi,
يونشى ،
since you've decided to leave,
منذ أن قررت المغادرة ،
♫Smiling under the umbrella brings back the longing again♫
الابتسام تحت المظلة يعيد الشوق من جديد
you can no longer blame him for anything he does.
لم يعد بإمكانك لومه على أي شيء يفعله.
♫The one with desire can't help that the other does not reciprocate♫
من لديه رغبة لا يستطيع أن يساعده أن الآخر لا يبادله
♫Heartbreaking zither music fills my dream for the rest of my life♫
موسيقى آلة القانون المفجعة تملأ حلمي لبقية حياتي
♫There is no cure for the romantic longing that causes inconsolable heartache♫
♫ لا يوجد علاج للشوق الرومانسي الذي يسبب وجع قلب لا يطاق
♫Clearly interested but biased against the one with desire♫
مهتم بوضوح لكنه متحيز ضد صاحب الرغبة
Young Master, you're awake.
السيد الشاب ، أنت مستيقظ.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I ran into you last night.
صادفتك الليلة الماضية.
You were drinking and looked upset.
كنت تشرب وتبدو مستاءً.
I wanted to comfort you,
أردت أن أريحك ،
but…
لكن…
You held my hand and wouldn't let me go.
أمسكت بيدي ولن تدعني أذهب.
I had to stay here to take care of you.
كان علي أن أبقى هنا لأعتني بك.
Sorry
آسف
for what I did last night.
لما فعلته الليلة الماضية.
I apologize.
أنا أعتذر.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
If anything bothers you in the future,
إذا كان هناك أي شيء يزعجك في المستقبل ،
don't hesitate to confide in me.
لا تتردد في الوثوق بي.
Wuyan.
الرقبة.
Please forgive me
رجائاً أعطني
if I offended you last night.
إذا أساءت إليك الليلة الماضية.
We both have someone we love.
كلانا لديه شخص نحبه.
It's inappropriate for us
إنه غير مناسب لنا
to be in the same room.
أن تكون في نفس الغرفة.
I stayed of my own accord…
بقيت من رغبتي ...
My third brother
أخي الثالث
is in deep love with you.
في حالة حب عميق معك.
Please don't let him down.
من فضلك لا تخذله.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You look annoyed.
تبدو منزعجًا.
Everyone is saying
الجميع يقول
that Young Master and Miss Nangong
أن السيد الشاب والآنسة Nangong
spent last night together in the hotel.
قضينا الليلة الماضية معًا في الفندق.
It's just a rumor.
إنها مجرد شائعة.
Siyan is well-educated
سيان متعلم جيدًا
[Hongan Clinic]
[عيادة هونغان]
and never did anything ill-mannered.
ولم يفعلوا شيئًا سيئًا.
My brother only cares about Yunxi.
أخي يهتم فقط بـ Yunxi.
How's it possible
كيف يكون ذلك ممكنا
that they spent the night
أنهم قضوا الليل
in the same room?
في نفس الغرفه؟
But people in the hotel
لكن الناس في الفندق
saw it.
رايتها.
Rumors have spread all over the city.
انتشرت الشائعات في جميع أنحاء المدينة.
There must be a misunderstanding.
يجب أن يكون هناك سوء فهم.
They
أنهم
would never do such a thing.
لن تفعل مثل هذا الشيء.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
I intended
كنت انوي
to keep these things from you forever.
للحفاظ على هذه الأشياء عنك إلى الأبد.
Miss Nangong
ملكة جمال نانغونغ
has been very close to Young Master recently.
كان قريبًا جدًا من Young Master مؤخرًا.
She visited Young Master's mansion alone many times.
زارت قصر يونغ ماستر وحدها عدة مرات.
There have been rumors in the city.
كانت هناك شائعات في المدينة.
I'll go ask Siyan about it.
سأذهب واسأل Siyan عن ذلك.
Jewelry for sale!
مجوهرات للبيع!
Take a look.
إلق نظرة.
The girl just now is quite hot.
الفتاة ساخنة جدا الآن.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
Stop!
قف!
What the heck?
ي للرعونة؟
You can't bump into someone and just walk away.
لا يمكنك أن تصطدم بشخص ما وتبتعد عنه.
Apologies.
اعتذارات.
It's you!
انه انت!
Dr. Xian, right?
دكتور زيان ، صحيح؟
Dr. Xian,
الدكتور زيان ،
everyone says you're humble and polite.
الجميع يقول أنك متواضع ومهذب.
But look at you.
لكن انظر إليك.
You bumped into me and are giving me dirty looks.
لقد اصطدمت بي وتعطيني نظرة قذرة.
Maybe Dr. Xian is in a hurry
ربما يكون الدكتور زيان في عجلة من أمره
to treat someone's wife.
لمعاملة زوجة شخص ما.
You got in his way.
لقد حصلت في طريقه.
Of course he's giving you dirty looks.
بالطبع هو يعطيك نظرة قذرة.
Stop!
قف!
Move.
يتحرك.
Are you angry?
هل أنت غاضب؟
Don't consider yourself superior
لا تعتبر نفسك متفوقا
just because you're the Master's son.
فقط لأنك ابن السيد.
Your mother was just a maid.
كانت والدتك مجرد خادمة.
Have you taken yourself as a Young Master?
هل اعتبرت نفسك سيدًا شابًا؟
You want to fight with us?
تريد القتال معنا؟
We don't have the balls
ليس لدينا الكرات
to fight someone as fragile as you.
لمحاربة شخص ضعيف مثلك.
What if you get hurt and blackmail us？
ماذا لو تأذيت وابتزتنا？
You should die
يجب أن تموت
and reincarnate as a stronger man.
ويتجسد كرجل أقوى.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Stop! Stop!
قف!  قف!
Spare me!
اعفنى!
Please show me mercy, Dr. Xian.
من فضلك أرني الرحمة يا دكتور زيان.
Spare my life!
تجنيب حياتي!
I'm a jerk.
أنا أحمق.
Please spare my life, Dr. Xian.
أرجوك أنقذ حياتي يا دكتور (زيان).
Spare my life!
تجنيب حياتي!
Please.
لو سمحت.
♫Can we just keep quiet♫
♫ هل يمكننا فقط التزام الصمت
♫And enjoy the scenery♫
♫ واستمتع بالمناظر ♫
♫It is better than any expression of words♫
أفضل من أي تعبير بالكلام
♫Can we just keep quiet♫
♫ هل يمكننا فقط التزام الصمت
♫And keep it in our memory♫
واحتفظ بها في ذاكرتنا ♫
♫Let's preserve the most beautiful moment♫
♫ لنحافظ على أجمل لحظة
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Why are you
لماذا انت
so cruel to me?
قاسية جدا بالنسبة لي؟
[Fate]
[قدر]
♫I wish to hold your hand♫
♫ أتمنى أن أمسك بيدك ♫
♫Till the end of the day♫
♫ حتى نهاية اليوم ♫
Our strings were tied onto it.
كانت خيوطنا مقيدة به.
Now our wishes
الآن رغباتنا
will come true.
سوف يتحقق.
♫But I can't escape from fate♫
♫ لكنني لا أستطيع الهروب من القدر
♫In the end, we will part♫
♫ في النهاية سوف نفترق ♫
♫Can we just keep quiet♫
♫ هل يمكننا فقط التزام الصمت
You held my hand.
أمسكت بيدي.
♫And enjoy the scenery♫
♫ واستمتع بالمناظر ♫
It means you agree to be with me.
هذا يعني أنك توافق على أن تكون معي.
Fate Tree,
شجرة القدر
thank you.
شكرا لك.
♫It is better than any expression of words♫
أفضل من أي تعبير بالكلام
♫Can we just keep quiet♫
♫ هل يمكننا فقط التزام الصمت
♫And keep it in our memory♫
واحتفظ بها في ذاكرتنا ♫
♫Let's preserve the most beautiful moment♫
♫ لنحافظ على أجمل لحظة
He bullied
تخويف
the powerless supervision guards
حراس الإشراف الضعفاء
just because he's the Master's son.
فقط لأنه ابن السيد.
He presumed too much.
لقد افترض الكثير.
The guards' family
عائلة الحراس
submitted complaints to me.
قدم لي شكاوى.
They want me to do them justice.
يريدون مني أن أنصفهم.
Even if I want to help Xian,
حتى لو أردت مساعدة زيان ،
I can't prevent
لا أستطيع منع ذلك
rumors from spreading.
شائعات عن الانتشار.
As his mother,
كوالدته ،
you can criticize or punish him
يمكنك انتقاده أو معاقبته
for his mistake.
لخطئه.
It's not difficult.
انها ليست صعبة.
The blunder
الخطأ الفادح
Xi'er made
صنع Xi'er
is what we should be fretting over.
هو ما يجب أن نقلق بشأنه.
The whole city
المدينة باجمعها
is talking about the night
يتحدث عن الليل
he spent with Miss Nangong.
قضى مع الآنسة Nangong.
Miss Nangong's reputation is ruined.
دمرت سمعة ملكة جمال Nangong.
The construction of the city will soon be completed.
سيتم الانتهاء قريبا من بناء المدينة.
Nangong Shi's granddaughter
حفيدة نانغونغ شي
really knows how to seize the opportunity.
يعرف حقًا كيف يغتنم الفرصة.
Xi'er has always disliked
Xi'er لم يعجبه دائمًا
us mentioning his marriage.
بذكر زواجه.
Why should I bother him?
لماذا يجب أن أزعجه؟
When you tried to make a match
عندما حاولت أن تجعل المباراة
between Fengyi and Xi'er,
بين Fengyi و Xi'er ،
you didn't seem to be afraid of annoying him.
لا يبدو أنك تخشى مضايقته.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
You think I don't know
تعتقد أنني لا أعرف
what you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Anyway,
على أي حال،
Xi'er's marriage
زواج زير
can't be postponed anymore.
لا يمكن تأجيلها بعد الآن.
As I said,
كما قلت،
give both of these two girls
تعطي كل من هاتين الفتاتين
to him.
له.
Whoever gives birth first
من يلد أولا
will be the first lady.
ستكون السيدة الأولى.
I don't think anyone dares to have an opinion.
لا أعتقد أن أي شخص يجرؤ على إبداء رأي.
It's quite sweet.
إنه حلو جدا.
By the grace of God, here is Master's edict.
بفضل الله ، هذا هو مرسوم السيد.
Xiao Fengyi is gentle, kind, honest, sincere
شياو فنجي لطيف ، لطيف ، صادق ، صادق
and good-looking.
وحسن المظهر.
Nangong Siyan
نانغونغ سيان
is talented and elegant.
موهوب وأنيق.
These two girls are waiting to get married,
هاتان الفتاتان تنتظران الزواج ،
and are excellent in talent, appearance and conduct.
وممتازون في الموهبة والمظهر والسلوك.
I hereby bestow marriage to Young Master Jiang Chaoxi.
بموجب هذا أمنح الزواج من السيد الشاب جيانغ تشوكسي.
You shall get married on a good day.
يجب أن تتزوج في يوم جيد.
In the future,
فى المستقبل،
whoever gives birth first
من يلد أولا
will be the first lady,
ستكون السيدة الأولى ،
and the other will be the second lady.
والأخرى ستكون السيدة الثانية.
You shall manage the family together
يجب أن تدير الأسرة معًا
with Young Master.
مع السيد الشاب.
It's the luck of the people in Cangyue.
إنه حظ الناس في كانغيو.
Congratulations, Young Master.
مبروك يا سيد الشباب.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Jiang Chaoxi.
جيانغ تشوكسي.
Where is Yunxi?
أين هو يونكسي؟
Where is Miss Yunxi?
أين الآنسة يونكسي؟
You must know it
يجب أن تعرف ذلك
better than anyone, Mr. Fusheng.
أفضل من أي شخص آخر ، السيد فوشينغ.
Last night, she held you
الليلة الماضية ، احتجزتك
to bill and coo.
للفواتير والسجع.
But now,
لكن الآن،
you ask us where she is?
تسألنا أين هي؟
That's not necessary to look around.
هذا ليس من الضروري أن ننظر حولنا.
You can't escape from here,
لا يمكنك الهروب من هنا ،
and Jiang Chaoxi won't be able to find you.
ولن يتمكن جيانغ تشوكسي من إيجادك.
Since Commander Xiao wants to see me,
بما أن القائد (شياو) يريد رؤيتي
you can ask me to go to your mansion.
يمكنك أن تطلب مني الذهاب إلى القصر الخاص بك.
Why are you making such a fuss?
لماذا تثير كل هذه الجلبة؟
Stop playing dumb.
توقف عن اللعب الغبي.
I didn't bring you here
أنا لم أحضرك إلى هنا
to treat you to a meal.
لمعاملة لك وجبة.
Give me the white jade comb.
أعطني مشط اليشم الأبيض.
The white jade comb?
مشط اليشم الأبيض؟
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Commander Xiao, if you want a comb,
القائد شياو ، إذا كنت تريد مشطًا ،
you can buy one on the street.
يمكنك شراء واحدة في الشارع.
Why did you ask me for it?
لماذا طلبت مني ذلك؟
You know it clearly.
أنت تعرف ذلك بوضوح.
What I want
ماذا اريد
is the white jade comb
هو مشط اليشم الأبيض
which you take with you.
الذي تأخذه معك.
It's the key to the Fengchi.
إنه مفتاح Fengchi.
I advise you
أنا أنصحك
not to be unperceptive
ألا تكون غير مدرك
like your father
مثل والدك
and your brother.
واخوكم.
What?
ماذا؟
My white jade comb
مشط اليشم الأبيض
is the key to finding Fengchi.
هو مفتاح العثور على Fengchi.
I wouldn't know if you didn't tell me.
لن أعرف إذا لم تخبرني.
Unfortunately, you're late.
لسوء الحظ ، لقد تأخرت.
That white jade comb
مشط اليشم الأبيض
has been sent to Young Master
تم إرساله إلى السيد الشاب
as a token of love.
كرمز للحب.
Why don't you let me go?
لماذا لا تدعني اذهب
I'll ask Young Master for it
سأطلب من السيد الشاب ذلك
and send it to you.
وأرسلها لك.
Do you think I'm stupid?
هل تعتقد أنا غبي؟
But the white jade comb
لكن مشط اليشم الأبيض
is really not with me.
حقا ليس معي.
Didn't Pepper search for it
لم Pepper البحث عنها
just now?
الآن؟
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
Let Pepper go back
دع الفلفل يعود
and steal it again.
ويسرقها مرة أخرى.
Anyway, she is quite familiar with
على أي حال ، فهي مألوفة تمامًا
the Young Master's Mansion.
قصر السيد الشاب.
It seems that you really think I'm stupid.
يبدو أنك تعتقد حقًا أنني غبي.
If so,
لو ذلك،
Jiang Chaoxi
جيانغ تشوكسي
will know directly
سيعرف مباشرة
that you are in my hands
أنك في يدي
and he will come to save you.
وسوف يأتي ليخلصك.
Then what do you want to do?
ثم ماذا تريد ان تفعل؟
Why don't you just use me
لماذا لا تستخدمني فقط
to threaten Young Master
لتهديد السيد الشاب
and ask him to hand over the white jade comb?
وتطلب منه تسليم مشط اليشم الأبيض؟
I think with his love for me,
أعتقد بحبه لي ،
he will definitely agree.
سيوافق بالتأكيد.
Jiang Chaoxi.
جيانغ تشوكسي.
I told you at first
لقد أخبرتك في البداية
if you didn't love Yunxi anymore,
إذا لم تكن تحب Yunxi بعد الآن ،
you should give her back to me.
يجب أن تعيدها إلي.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
You promised me
لقد وعدتني
that day would never come.
ذلك اليوم لن يأتي أبدا.
It's only been a few days.
لقد مرت بضعة أيام فقط.
How can you let Yunxi down?
كيف يمكنك أن تدع Yunxi يسقط؟
Tang Qing.
تانغ تشينغ.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
How do you know
كيف علمت بذلك
I'm the one who betrayed?
أنا من خان؟
You are not the one?
انت لست الواحد؟
You are not the one who spent the night
أنت لست الشخص الذي قضى الليل
alone with Nangong Siyan in the tavern?
وحده مع Nangong Siyan في الحانة؟
Aren't you the one
ألست أنت
who gladly accepted the marriage given by Master?
من الذي قبل زواج سيده بكل سرور؟
Today,
اليوم،
I will seek justice for Yunxi.
سأسعى لتحقيق العدالة لـ Yunxi.
Tang Qing.
تانغ تشينغ.
Our priority is to find Yunxi.
أولويتنا هي إيجاد Yunxi.
We must unite and focus on one goal.
يجب أن نتحد ونركز على هدف واحد.
Don't create more troubles.
لا تخلق المزيد من المشاكل.
Yunxi is weak now.
Yunxi ضعيف الآن.
If anything happens,
إذا حدث أي شيء ،
she won't be able to hold on.
لن تكون قادرة على الصمود.
If anything happens to Yunxi,
إذا حدث أي شيء لـ Yunxi ،
I won't forgive you.
لن أسامحك.
Yunxi is rational,
Yunxi عقلاني ،
so she won't leave without saying goodbye.
لذلك لن تغادر دون أن تقول وداعًا.
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
she has met someone bad.
لقد قابلت شخصًا سيئًا.
Yunxi.
يونشى.
Someone bad...
شخص سيء ...
Oh no.
أوه لا.
Lord.
رب.
I have something to report.
لدي شيء للإبلاغ عنه.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Master ordered
أمر سيد
to marry Miss Fengyi and Nangong Siyan
للزواج من الآنسة Fengyi و Nangong Siyan
to Young Master at the same time.
إلى السيد الشاب في نفس الوقت.
How did he react?
كيف كان رد فعله؟
Young Master has received the decree.
تلقى السيد الشاب المرسوم.
It seems that
يبدو أن
you overestimated yourself.
لقد بالغت في تقدير نفسك.
Get over yourself.
تمالك نفسك.
You're missing.
أنت مفتقد.
Instead of looking for you,
بدلا من البحث عنك ،
Jiang Chaoxi accepted the wedding
قبل جيانغ تشوكسي حفل الزفاف
with joy.
ببهجة.
Are you stupid?
هل انت غبي؟
Tell me quickly.
قل لي بسرعة.
Where is the white jade comb?
أين مشط اليشم الأبيض؟
I told you I gave it to Jiang Chaoxi.
أخبرتك أنني أعطيتها لجيانغ تشوكسي.
To deal with
لكى تتعامل مع
a stubborn girl like you,
فتاة عنيدة مثلك ،
it seems that
يبدو أن
we need to use some means.
نحتاج إلى استخدام بعض الوسائل.
Steward.
ستيوارد.
Yes.
نعم.
-You won't tell me, right? -My Lord.
-لن تخبرني ، أليس كذلك؟  -ربي.
Yunxi has the poison of heartburn,
يونكسي لديه سم حرقة ،
so her body isn't as good as ordinary people.
لذا فإن جسدها ليس جيدًا مثل الناس العاديين.
I'm afraid she won't be able to stand a few whips.
أخشى أنها لن تكون قادرة على الوقوف ببعض السياط.
If she dies,
إذا ماتت ،
isn't there less chance
ليس هناك فرصة أقل
of finding the white jade comb?
من إيجاد مشط اليشم الأبيض؟
Let me talk to her.
اسمحوا لي أن أتحدث معها.
After all, I've been with her for so long.
بعد كل شيء ، لقد كنت معها لفترة طويلة.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll give you some time.
سأعطيك بعض الوقت.
Don't let me down.
لا تخذلني.
Yes.
نعم.
You are really an excellent spy.
أنت حقا جاسوس ممتاز.
Your disguise was perfect.
كان تمويهك مثاليًا.
I used to treat you
اعتدت على معاملتك
as my good friend.
كصديقي العزيز.
Yunxi,
يونشى ،
I advise you not to go against Commander Xiao.
أنصحك بعدم الذهاب ضد القائد شياو.
Or it's you
أو أنت
who suffer.
الذين يعانون.
As long as you tell me,
ما دمت تخبرني ،
I'll ask Commander to let you go.
سأطلب من القائد أن يتركك تذهب.
You are so naive.
أنت ساذج جدا.
Whether I say it or not,
سواء قلت ذلك أم لا ،
I'll die.
سوف اموت.
I can live a few more days if I don't say it.
يمكنني أن أعيش بضعة أيام أخرى إذا لم أقل ذلك.
Search the whole city
ابحث في المدينة كلها
and get Yunxi back.
واستعد Yunxi.
Search!
يبحث!
Yes.
نعم.
Yunxi! Yunxi! Yunxi!
Yunxi! Yunxi! Yunxi!
Yunxi!
يونشى!
Sister Yunxi! Yunxi!
الأخت يونشى!
Yunxi. Yunxi.
يونشى.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
You go this way.
تذهب بهذه الطريقة.
You three go there
أنتم الثلاثة يذهبون إلى هناك
and ask around
واسأل من حولك
if any woman fell into the water.
إذا سقطت أي امرأة في الماء.
Go.
يذهب.
Yes.
نعم.
Yunxi! Sister Yunxi! Yunxi!
يونشى! الأخت يونشى! يونشى!
Sister Yunxi! Yunxi! Yunxi!
الأخت يونشى! يونشى! يونشى!
[Nangong's Mansion]
[قصر نانغونغ]
Grandpa.
الجد.
Siyan.
شراء.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Siyan,
يشتري،
Master has issued a decree for marriage,
اصدر المعلم قرارا بالزواج ،
and Young Master has no objection.
والشاب ليس لديه اعتراض.
I'm
انا
finally relieved.
بالارتياح أخيرا.
I know you don't want to.
أعلم أنك لا تريد ذلك.
But...
ولكن...
No.
رقم.
Grandpa.
الجد.
I'm willing to marry him.
أنا على استعداد للزواج منه.
I'm willing to
أنا على استعداد ل
follow the arrangement of Master and Grandpa.
اتبع ترتيب السيد والجد.
Good!
جيد!
My dear granddaughter
حفيدتي العزيزة
has grown up.
كبر.
I'm very pleased.
أنا مسرور جدا.
I'm happy for you.
انا سعيد لأجلك.
Father.
أب.
I won't marry him!
لن أتزوجه!
I will never marry my cousin!
لن أتزوج ابنة عمي!
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Stop making noises!
توقف عن إصدار الضجيج!
No!
رقم!
I don't care. I won't marry him.
لا أهتم.  لن أتزوجه.
Enough.
كافية.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
I really want you
أنا حقا أريدك
to marry Jiang Chaoxi?
للزواج من جيانغ تشوكسي؟
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
Let's go to Aunt and Uncle
دعنا نذهب إلى العمة والعم
and cancel the marriage.
وإلغاء الزواج.
No.
رقم.
Are you really stupid?
هل انت حقا غبي؟
It's Master's order.
إنه أمر الماجستير.
Can you change it easily?
هل يمكنك تغييره بسهولة؟
Enough.
كافية.
Let
يترك
me
أنا
think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
When you're done,
حينما تنتهي،
the bridal sedan will be at the door.
ستكون سيدان الزفاف عند الباب.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I'll go find Cousin myself.
سأذهب لأجد ابن عمي بنفسي.
I will ask him to beg Uncle
سأطلب منه أن يتوسل العم
to cancel the marriage.
لإلغاء الزواج.
Stop!
قف!
Father!
أب!
Listen.
استمع.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you'll stay here
ستبقى هنا
and you are not allowed to go anywhere.
ولا يسمح لك بالذهاب إلى أي مكان.
Guards!
حراس!
Father!
أب!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I didn't do anything wrong.
لم أفعل أي شيء خاطئ.
Why won't you let me go out?
لماذا لا تدعني أخرج؟
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Take her back to her room.
أعدها إلى غرفتها.
No.
رقم.
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
Let go!
اتركه!
No.
رقم.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
-My girl! -I'm not getting married.
-فتاتي!  - أنا لن أتزوج.
I'm going to see Cousin.
انا ذاهب لرؤية ابن العم.
Lord.
رب.
Lady has been engaged to Young Master.
تمت خطبة السيدة إلى السيد الشاب.
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
Since
حيث
Jiang Chaoxi has agreed to the marriage,
وافق جيانغ تشوكسي على الزواج ،
that means Yunxi
هذا يعني يونكسي
is not that important in his heart.
ليس بهذه الأهمية في قلبه.
If he knows what's good for him,
إذا كان يعرف ما هو جيد بالنسبة له ،
I may
انا ممكن
give him another chance.
أعطه فرصة أخرى.
Xiao Huasheng.
شياو هوا شنغ.
Give Yunxi back to me!
أعد Yunxi إلي!
Young Master, you call my name
سيد الشباب ، أنت تنادي اسمي
very smoothly.
بسلاسة شديدة.
Where did you learn the etiquette?
أين تعلمت الآداب؟
How dare you speak in a loud voice
كيف تجرؤ على التحدث بصوت عال
in my mansion?
في قصري؟
Did you
هل فعلت
kidnap Yunxi?
خطف يونشى؟
Do you have any evidence?
هل لديك أي دليل؟
Don't talk nonsense
لا تتحدث عن هراء
without evidence.
بدون دليل.
I knew you wouldn't admit it.
كنت أعلم أنك لن تعترف بذلك.
Since you don't feel guilty,
بما أنك لا تشعر بالذنب ،
why don't you let me
لماذا لا تدعني
search in your mansion?
البحث في القصر الخاص بك؟
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Although you're Young Master,
على الرغم من أنك سيد صغير ،
I am also your uncle.
انا ايضا عمك
I will also be your father-in-law.
سأكون أيضا والد زوجتك.
How can you humiliate me like this?
كيف يمكنك إذلالني هكذا؟
What?
ماذا؟
You dare not let me search?
أنت لا تجرؤ على السماح لي بالبحث؟
Search.
يبحث.
You can search.
يمكنك البحث.
I can let you
يمكنني السماح لك
search at will
البحث في الإرادة
in my mansion.
في قصري.
But I have to remind you.
لكن علي أن أذكرك.
What will happen
ماذا سيحدث
if you can't find Yunxi here?
إذا لم تجد Yunxi هنا؟
Young man,
شاب،
don't be so reckless.
لا تكن متهورًا جدًا.
Especially you
خصوصا أنت
are Young Master.
هم سيد الشباب.
Every choice you make
كل خيار تقوم به
will affect
سيؤثر
your future.
مستقبلك.
I advise you not to be impulsive
أنصحك ألا تكون متسرعًا
and do something
وتفعل شيئًا
you will regret for the rest of your life.
سوف تندم لبقية حياتك.
I've already made my decision.
لقد اتخذت قراري بالفعل.
In the past,
في الماضي،
for the sake of my mother's upbringing,
من أجل تربية والدتي ،
I didn't blame you
أنا لم ألومك
for what you had done.
على ما فعلته.
But you really shouldn't
لكن لا يجب عليك فعلاً
hurt Yunxi.
تؤذي Yunxi.
Xiao Huasheng,
شياو هواشنغ
you'd better pray
من الأفضل أن تصلي
I won't find any evidence.
لن أجد أي دليل.
According to Xiao Huasheng's reaction today,
وفقًا لرد فعل Xiao Huasheng اليوم ،
I'm sure
أنا متأكد
Yunxi is in his hands.
يونشى بين يديه.
But he didn't hide her in the Xiao's Mansion.
لكنه لم يخفها في قصر شياو.
So
لذا
Xiao Huasheng must have captured Yunxi
يجب أن يكون Xiao Huasheng قد استولى على Yunxi
for Fengchi.
من أجل Fengchi.
For Fengchi?
من أجل Fengchi؟
But how can Yunxi
ولكن كيف يمكن Yunxi
know where Fengchi is?
تعرف أين Fengchi؟
If she knew earlier,
إذا علمت في وقت سابق ،
why did she bother
لماذا تهتم
to find the map in the Xiao's Mansion?
للعثور على الخريطة في قصر شياو؟
Yunxi
يونشى
really gave you the white jade comb.
أعطاك حقًا مشط اليشم الأبيض.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
You still don't understand.
ما زلت لا تفهم.
This white jade comb is the key
مشط اليشم الأبيض هذا هو المفتاح
to find Fengchi.
للعثور على Fengchi.
Yunxi gave it to you
أعطاها لك Yunxi
not because she likes you?
ليس لانها معجبة بك؟
What's your relationship then?
ما علاقتك إذن؟
Why did she give you
لماذا أعطتك
such an important thing?
مثل هذا الشيء المهم؟
Luo Hexuan is my confidant.
لوه هيكسان هو صديقي.
Of course I treat Yunxi
بالطبع أنا أعالج Yunxi
as my own sister.
كأختي.
I see.
أرى.
But why did she lie to me?
لكن لماذا كذبت علي؟
Even though I misunderstood
على الرغم من أنني أسأت الفهم
your relationship,
علاقتك،
she didn't explain it to me.
لم تشرح لي ذلك.
Well,
نحن سوف،
you should ask
يجب أن تسأل
your good mother.
امك الطيبة.
What did she
ما فعلته أنها
tell Yunxi?
اقول يونشى؟
For your safety,
من أجل سلامتك ،
the only thing she could do is to leave you.
الشيء الوحيد الذي يمكنها فعله هو تركك.
So she still loves me.
لذلك ما زالت تحبني.
How dare you say you love Yunxi deeply?
كيف تجرؤ على القول إنك تحب يونكسي بعمق؟
You can't even feel
لا يمكنك حتى الشعور
her love for you.
حبها لك.
I was too stupid.
كنت غبيا جدا.
I doubted her love for me
شككت في حبها لي
and did so many things
وفعلت أشياء كثيرة
to hurt her.
ليؤذيها.
You should leave your confession
يجب عليك ترك اعترافك
to Yunxi.
إلى Yunxi.
Our top priority is to find a way
أولويتنا القصوى هي إيجاد طريقة
to get her out of Xiao Huasheng's hands.
لإخراجها من يدي شياو هوا شنغ.
Since we know it was Xiao Huasheng,
بما أننا نعلم أنه كان شياو هوا شنغ ،
why are we still sitting here?
لماذا ما زلنا نجلس هنا؟
Bring some men to the Xiao's Mansion
أحضر بعض الرجال إلى قصر شياو
and put a sword on his neck.
ووضع سيف على عنقه.
I don't believe he won't tell us.
لا أصدق أنه لن يخبرنا.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Wait.
انتظر.
Xiao Huasheng is cunning.
شياو هوا شنغ ماكر.
If we alert him,
إذا قمنا بتنبيهه ،
it may be bad for Yunxi.
قد يكون سيئا بالنسبة ليونكسي.
Then tell me
ثم قل لي
what we should do.
ما يجب ان نفعله.
There is someone
هناك شخص ما
who can help us.
من يمكنه مساعدتنا.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Where is the white jade comb?
أين مشط اليشم الأبيض؟
I...
أنا...
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
You're quite stubborn.
أنت عنيد جدا.
Let's see how long you can be stubborn.
دعونا نرى إلى متى يمكنك أن تكون عنيدًا.
Commander.
قائد.
Yunxi seems to have relapsed.
يبدو أن Yunxi قد انتكس.
She really can't stand
إنها حقًا لا تستطيع الوقوف
a few more hits.
عدد قليل من الزيارات.
Yunxi,
يونشى ،
just say it.
فقط قلها.
As long as you say it,
طالما قلت ذلك ،
you won't have to suffer anymore.
لن تضطر إلى المعاناة بعد الآن.
I really don't know.
أنا حقا لا أعرف.
Look.
نظرة.
I'll let you taste
سأتركك تتذوق
all the torture tools here
كل أدوات التعذيب هنا
one by one.
واحدا تلو الآخر.
I'll torture you slowly.
سوف أعذبك ببطء.
I'm not afraid that you won't tell me.
أنا لست خائفًا من أنك لن تخبرني.
Steward.
ستيوارد.
Give her some time.
امنحها بعض الوقت.
Don't let her die now.
لا تدعها تموت الآن.
Yunxi.
يونشى.
Wait.
انتظر.
Yunxi, I'm sorry.
يونشى ، أنا آسف.
I really treat you
أنا حقا أعاملك
as my good sister.
كأختي الفاضلة.
But
ولكن
I've been trained
لقد تدربت
to be loyal to Commander.
أن تكون مخلصًا للقائد.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
only you
أنت فقط
let me know what friendship is.
اسمحوا لي أن أعرف ما هي الصداقة.
But I...
لكن أنا...
But I made you
لكني صنعتك
like this.
مثله.
I'm really sorry.
أنا حقا آسف.
I just want to ask
انا فقط اريد ان اسال
whether Young Master has really accepted the marriage.
ما إذا كان السيد الشاب قد قبل الزواج حقًا.
Yunxi.
يونشى.